[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":116826,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":259303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":13909,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":273215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":27013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":300231,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3319,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":303553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":9303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":312858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1229,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":314088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the sec ond one  to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["60","6","0"],"rt":18611,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":332700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1593,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":334295,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4741,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":339038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1131,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":340170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":20445,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":360616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Corr ect! 3 + <sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1358,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":361976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":15675,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":377652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1398,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":379052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6< /sub> 3?  <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":384074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":3701,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":387777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger , you su btract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":6130,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":393909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1213,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":395124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":7588,"trial_type":"questi on","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":402714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1092,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":403807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":408275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1295,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":409572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":27716,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":437293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</su b>). Sim ilarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":45528,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":482823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":39262,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":522088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2025,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":524114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the invers e of 1 u nder +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3853,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":527969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1316,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":529286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":532299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1216,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":533516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":536444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4  = 0, an d 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1348,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":537794,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":541621,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1230,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":542853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the oper ation ca n simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":24043,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":566897,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub>  2 +<sub >6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":66833,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":633731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":641691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":3245,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":644938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub >? <br / ><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":647722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":9079,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":656802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under  +<sub>6 </sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":35592,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":692397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1436,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":693835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":9601,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":703437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3259,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":706697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practic e questi on with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":27762,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":734461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4270,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":738733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":2215,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":740949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4836,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":745787,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":14128,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":759917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":8179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":768097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":" ","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9","0"],"rt":11245,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":779343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":6812,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":786157,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":10088,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":796246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"because 4 + 1 =5, it is less than 9 so you don't subtract 9","explanation_history":["because 4 + 1 =5, it is less than 9 so you don't subtract 9"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":34742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":830989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4=12, 12 is higher than 9, so subtract 12-9 that = 3","explanation_history":["8=4","8=","8","8+4-","8+4=12, 12 is higher than 9, so subtract 12-9 that = 3"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":48707,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":879699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"when 0 is combined with any other number it gives that same number back","explanation_history":["0","when 0 is combined with any other number it gives that same numver","when 0 is combined with any other number it gives that same numve","when 0 is combined with any other number it gives that same numv","when 0 is combined with any other number it gives that same numeb","when 0 is combined with any other number it gives that same nume","when 0 is combined with any other number it gives that same number back"],"response_history":["0"],"rt":67169,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":946870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"fre e","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":20667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":967539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":5990,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":973530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":4305,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":977836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"W hat is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"i said 3 because the inverse is the number you add to the target to get the identity, like 3+6=9","explanation_history":["i said 3 because the inverse if","i said 3 because the inverse i","i said 3 because the inverse s t","i said 3 because the inverse s ","i said 3 because the inverse s","i said 3 because the inverse is the number you add to the indentiy","i said 3 because the inverse is the number you add to the target to get the identity, like 3+9","i said 3 because the inverse is the number you add to the target to get the identity, like 3+6=9"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":76576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1054413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in w ords how  you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no because if you add 2+0 you get 2, there is no way to get 1, 3 and so on","explanation_history":["no because if you add 2 and 0 you get","no because if you add 2 and 0 you ge","no because if you add 2 ","no because if you add 2+0 you get 2, there is no way to get 1, 3 and so on"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":115736,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1170151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"no, because there is no way for you to produce all of the numbers from 1-9 with 3 as a generator ","explanation_history":["no, bea","no, because there is no way fro you "," no, beca use there is no way fro you","no, because there is no way fro yo","no, because there is no way fro y","no, because there is no way fro ","no, because there is no way fro","no, because there is no way fr","no, because there is no way for ou","no, because there is no way for o","no, because there is no way for you rp","no, because there is no way for you r","no, because there is no way for you to pe","no, because there is no way for you to proudce","no, because there is no way for you to proudc","no, because there is no way for you to prouduce all of the numbers from 1-9 with 3 as a geneta","no, because there is no way for you to prouduce all of the numbers from 1-9 with 3 as a genet","no, because there is no way for you to prouduce all of the numbers from 1-9 with 3 as a generatop ","no, because there is no way for you to prouduce all of the numbers from 1-9 with 3 as a generatop","no, because there is no way for you to prouduce all of the numbers from 1-9 with 3 as a generat or ","no , because there is no way for you to produce all of the numbers from 1-9 with 3 as a generator "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":161872,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1332025,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't think it is possible to get the numbers 1-9 with 5 as a generator","explanation_history":["I don't think it is possible to get the numbers 1-9 with 5 as a generator"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":101893,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1433919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"yes, you can add all of the numbers meaning 6+1, to 6+9-9 =6, to get all the numbers in 1 through 9","explanation_history":["no nec","no ne","no n","no bea","no because, 6+5=11 -9, gives you 2,","65432087","ywa, you c","ywa, you ","ywa, you","ywa, yo","ywa, y","ywa, ","ywa,","ywa","yw","yes, you can add all of the number with ","yes, you can add all of the number with","yes, you can add all of the number wit","yes, you can add all of the number wi","yes, you can add all of the number w","yes, you can add all of the number ","yes, you can add all of the numbers meaning 6+1, to 6+9-9 =6, to get all the u","yes, you can add all of the numbers meaning 6+1, to 6+9-9 =6, to get all the numbers in 1-","yes, you can add all of the numbers meaning 6+1, to 6+9-9 =6, to get all the numbers in 1 through 8","yes, you can add all of the numbers meaning 6+1, to 6+9-9 =6, to get all the numbers in 1 through 9"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":330637,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1764558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":37119,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1801679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+0_n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0+ (","0+ +_n","0+ +_n","+_n","1+ ","1+ +_n","1+ _n","1+ _n","1+_n","1+0_n","1+0_n"],"rt":121357,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1923037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+_x= inverse","explain":true,"explanation":"I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you combine with the element to get the identity","explanation_history":["I am not sure how to explain my answer because I don't understand the question, but I'll explain my logc","I am not sure how to explain my answer because I don't understand the question, but I'll explain my logic","I choose this formula becaue ","I choose this formula becaue","I choose this formula because the inverse is thr","I choose this formula because the inverse is the","I choose this formula because the inverse is th","I choose this formula because the inverse is t","I choose this formula because  the inv erse is whatever number you use","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you us","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you u","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you cmobi","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you cmob","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you cmo","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you cm","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you combin ","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you combine with the element to egt the identity","I choose this formula because the inverse is whatever number you combine with the element to get the identity"],"response_history":["x=","x=","x=","x-","x=","x=","x=","x=","x+_n","x+","x+_n","x+_n","x+_","x+_x","x+_x= identif","x+_x= inverse"],"rt":280335,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2203373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I think that maybe certain numbers that are easily divisible may tell you if a generator under _n can make all elements","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I thikn","I thik","I think the pattern is odd numv","I think the pattern is odd numbers","I t","I did not notice a parr","I did not notice a par","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I fthi","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I fth","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I ft","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I f","I did not notice a pattern in the elemen t genera tors, I think that maybe certain numbers tht a","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I think that maybe certain numbers tht ","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I think that maybe certain numbers tht","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I think that maybe certain numbers thar","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I think that maybe certain numbers that are easily divisble may tell you if a generator under _n i","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I think that maybe certain numbers that are easily divisble may tell you if a generator under _n can make all elements","I did not notice a pattern in the element generators, I think that maybe certain numbers that are easily divisible may tell you if a generator under _n can make all elements"],"rt":246898,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2450273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Tru e or fal se: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":55202,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2505476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":4875,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2510353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":41874,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2552232,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"I think this is true because if the number is a divisor of n then you know it will readily go into the number multiple times allowing you to get x through whatever the divisor is, for example all the numbers in 1-4","explanation_history":["I thought of 6 as a generator","I thought of the examole","I thought of the examol","I thought of the examo","I thought of the examo","I thought of the example 1+ 3_6","I  couldn't think of an example to make this si","I couldn't think of an example to make this statement true, I d","I couldn't think of an example to make this statement tr","I think this is tu","I think this is true because if the numbb","I think this is true because if the number is a divsor","I think this is true because if the number is a divso","I think this is true because if the number is a divsisor of n then you know it will a","I think this is true because if the number is a divsisor of n then you know it will readily go into the number multiple times allowing you to get x through whatever the f","I think this is true because if the number is a divsisor of n then you know it will readily go into the number multiple times allowing you to get x through whatever the divisor its","I think this is true because if the number is a divsisor of n then you know it will readily go into the number multiple times allowing you to get x through whatever the divisor it","I think this  is true  because if the number is a divsisor of n then you know it will readily go into the number multiple times allowing you to get x through whatever the divisor is, for example all the numbers in 1-4","I think this is true because if the number is a divisor of n then you know it will readily go into the number multiple times allowing you to get x through whatever the divisor is, for example all the numbers in 1-4"],"response_history":["True","False","True"],"rt":220313,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2772547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":81451,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2854000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i am having trouble producing an example to explain this further","explanation_history":["I saif s","I saif ","I saif","I said sometimes because I figure that s","I said sometimes because I figure that there ia","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i am","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i a","I said sometimes because I figure that there is  almost  always a special rule in math, however i canno","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i cann","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i can","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i ca","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i c","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i am having trouble r","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i am having trouble pru","I said sometimes because I figure that there is almost always a special rule in math, however i am having trouble producing an example to explain this further"],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":89949,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2943951,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":17960,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2961913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1577,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2963492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"25","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["25"],"rt":2606,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2966100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":4460,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2970562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Business Accounting, Business Finance ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["F","a","Accounting ","Business Accounting, BUsien","Business Accounting, BUsie","Business Accounting, BUsi","Business Accounting, BUs","Business Accounting, BU","Business Accounting, Business Fianace ","Business Accounting, Business Finance "],"rt":30988,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3001552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":9553,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3011106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":9274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3020383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3945,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3024329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3029183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2961,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3032146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3034494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":5163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3039658,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no I did not","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no I did n ot"],"rt":6188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3045847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more examples and applications to further my understanding and explain myself","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I found it very hard to exo","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind ny ","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind ny","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind n","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I i","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the cp","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand th e concep ts, I n","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have like dmy","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have like dm","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have like d","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have like ","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more expa","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more exp","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more examples and applications to hl","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answ ers beca use I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more examples and applications to h","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more examples and applications to further my undert","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more examples and applications to further my undersa","I found it very hard to explain the logic behind my answers because I didn't understand the concepts, I would have liked more examples and applications to further my understanding and explain myself"],"rt":54823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":3100671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]